the music comes out tonight at 10 30 p.m when the moon when the gemini moon becomes a complete new
moon in the time zone that i'm in why why does a gemini moon matter on june 14th we have our
first lunation of the month which is a new moon in gemini at 24 degrees the ruler of the moon is
mercury and cancer and it's like very very close to perfecting this connection with mars and taurus
and that is energizing inspiring it feels action-oriented in that way gemini is the sign
of communication of language and some of our favorite emcees are gemini's hawk lauren hill
kendrick lamar my favorite emcee of all time andre 3000 i had no idea the immensity
of me dropping this album on june 14th the new moon in gemini i had just decided that
because i do things on new moons but i didn't know
the greatness of doing that on a particular gemini in new moon so i am conscious of the way
the planets are aligning for where we are in this world i am conscious of the way the planets are
aligned for my soul to do its work and its assignments and it feels really fabulous to
also have worked with an engineer who understood when i said this has to come out on june 14th
and matt cody said that ain't a lot of time but we gonna make it on time
we did it
yeah
ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha
You